Ivan Giovanni Rojas

Tampa, FL 33607 | Cell: (813) 647-4892 | impetus1@gmx.com

Summary:

Prior and ongoing experience in web design with practice in full stack development which influenced freelance opportunities.

Fundamental skills in computer science abstractions and multiple computer programs. Diligent critical thinking skills with multitasking exceptional customer service capabilities.

<u>Areas of Expertise:</u>

Sound knowledge in Web Frameworks and libraries to include Vanilla Javascript| Node.Js| React JS| MERN|

JQuery| Adobe Suite| MS Office| WordPress| Joomla| Powershell| PyTorch| Docker| Google Cloud| Git

versioning| Python Django| BSD/Linux

3D dental scanning, designing, and printing (Autodesk Inventor)

Expertise in appliance repairs and logistics.

Front-end design creativity and agile project engagement
Rapid troubleshooting skills and analytical thinking; routing and middleware
Familiar with enterprise software ERP (Odoo)

Experience:

Freelance Developer February 2016 - Present | Tampa, FL

Rapid prototype and fullstack website development in React, Node, Express, and MongoDB.

Projects in web designs and app developments

Trial and error practices in different

As a freelance developer, I work with various different resources to help achieve their development goals Freelance clients include Mile2, Eric Seidel Media, Microstar Computers, and others.

Appliance Technician, Florida Free Appliance Pick-up January 2015 - October 2019 | Tampa, FL Spearheaded Startup in 2015.

Responsible for daily pick-up orders and maintaining a proper work schedule for a team of four. Managed control of company vehicles and upkeep. Periodic trips to a recycling facility to properly dispose of non-salvageable material. Observing safety standards for hazardous materials and heavy lifting. Troubleshooting and repairs on appliances ready for retail sale. Performed sales with second hand shops interested in negotiations.

Web Design/IT Administrator, Mile2 Cyber Security Training January 2016 - October 2016 | Tampa, FL

Completed assignments in Photoshop imagery. Managed Joomla CMS while designing custom plugins for MVC through Javascript. Supervised VMware virtual machines for load balancing and consuming into a commercial CentOS server. Responsible for version control, backups and SEO HTML metadata and keywords.

IT Assistant/Scanner, Bayshore Dental Studio, June 2013 - November 2013 | Tampa, FL

Assisted in 3D Dental scanning of patients, designs and prints of 3D images, and Network troubleshooting for office computers and technologies with exceptional front of the house customer service

Education and Training:

Autodidact

2013-present

Coursera online, 2016-2019 Linear Algebra through Python Machine Learning Udacity online, 2018 Practical Deep Learning for Coders Introduction to Computer Science

Hillsborough Community College, 2015-2016

Engineering Technologies/Computer Science

Won first place with a team in the HCC Electrathon race (2015)

Gary Adult High School, 2015

Hillsborough High School 2009-2013

Outreach Opportunities:

Tampa Bay Harvest, May 2015 - December 2019- Helped give out food Hillsborough High School Robotics Program | FIRST Alumni Robotics mentor Github.com/impetus1

https://floridafreeappliancepickup.com

Code for Tampa Bay| Civic Hacking - 2020